[
  {
    "question": "What is Ahead of Time Compiler in Java?",
    "choice1": "Ahead of time compiler compiles java files as and when you type and save.",
    "choice2": "Ahead of time compiler turns byte code to executable code line by line based on requirement",
    "choice3": "Ahead of time compiler is a replacement for JIT compiler to translate all byte code to a single executable file or code to run the program fast and efficient.",
    "choice4": "None of the above",
    "answer": "3",
    "link": "What-is-Ahead-of-Time-Compiler-in-Java.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Java command used to compile a java program from Command Line or Command Prompt or CMD?",
    "choice1": ">java hello.java",
    "choice2": ">javac hello.java",
    "choice3": ">javacomp hello.java",
    "choice4": ">javacmd hello.java",
    "answer": "2",
    "link": "What-is-the-Java-comand-used-to-compile-a-java-program-from-Comand-Line-or-Comand-Prompt-or-CMD.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the command used to Run a Java program form Command Line or Command Prompt or CMD?",
    "choice1": "javac hello",
    "choice2": "java hello.class",
    "choice3": "java hello",
    "choice4": "java hello.java",
    "answer": "3",
    "link": "What-is-the-comand-used-to-Run-a-Java-program-form-Comand-Line-or-Comand-Prompt-or-CMD.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "Every statement in Java language should end with a?",
    "choice1": "Dot or Period",
    "choice2": "Comma",
    "choice3": "Semicolon",
    "choice4": "Colon",
    "answer": "3",
    "link": "Every-statement-in-Java-language-should-end-with-a.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "A function in C language is similar to what in Java language?",
    "choice1": "Method",
    "choice2": "Member",
    "choice3": "Variable",
    "choice4": "None of the above",
    "answer": "1",
    "link": "A-function-in-C-language-is-similar-to-what-in-Java-language.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "All methods and variables in Java language are kept inside a?",
    "choice1": "File",
    "choice2": "Class or Interface",
    "choice3": "static method",
    "choice4": "main",
    "answer": "2",
    "link": "Al-methods-and-variables-in-Java-language-are-kept-inside-a.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the need to mention 'static' before main method?",
    "choice1": "To call main method without creating an object of class",
    "choice2": "To make main method as class method common to all instances",
    "choice3": " Both A and B",
    "choice4": "None of the above",
    "answer": "3",
    "link": "What-is-the-ned-to-mention-static-before-main-method.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "In standalone Java applications, which method is mandatory?",
    "choice1": "main method",
    "choice2": "show method",
    "choice3": "display method",
    "choice4": "print method",
    "answer": "1",
    "link": "In-standalone-Java-aplications-which-method-is-mandatory.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the use of Access modifier 'pubic' in Java language?",
    "choice1": "To hide the main method from misuse",
    "choice2": "To call the main method outside of Class or Package by JVM",
    "choice3": "To protect main method",
    "choice4": "None of the above",
    "answer": "2",
    "link": "What-is-the-use-of-Aces-modifier-pubic-in-Java-language.html"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the default return type of a method in Java language?",
    "choice1": "void",
    "choice2": "int",
    "choice3": "short",
    "choice4": "None of the above",
    "answer": "4",
    "link": "What-is-the-default-return-type-of-a-method-in-Java-language.html"
  }
]
